Guide to the Alan Pryce-Jones Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, [ca.1914]-96; Series II; 6.5; (16 boxes)
  - NOTEBOOKS
    - Holograph notes removed from Aragon, Chroniques du bel canto (Geneva: Albert Skira, [1947]) [cataloged separately], n.d. (Box 43, Folder 2005a)
  - WRITINGS OF OTHERS
    Arranged alphabetically
    - Almedingen, E. M.
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 1, folder 17
    - Birley, Eric, "Überlegungen zur Geschichte des römischen Heeres," printed pamphlet, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 2006)
    - Borchard, Ruth
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 3, Folder 131
    - Bray, Barbara
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 3, Folder 148
    - Brock, Edwin
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 3, Folder 158
    - Campbell, Roy
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 7, Folder 232
    - Dawnay, Alan, poems, 1910, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2007)
      "The People (a Prophecy)," printed
      "A Ballad of Ramillies Barracks,"
      typescript carbon and printed copy
      annotated by Vere Pryce-Jones
    - Emery, Jane
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 9, Folder 386
    - Flores, Angel, "Felisberto Hernandez," typescript mimeograph (Box 44, Folder 2008)
    - [Gathorne-Hardy, General Sir John?], [comic poem about World War I], manuscript, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2009)
    - Hales, Madge, typescript poems, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2010)
    - Hartmann, Cyril Hughes, essay, "Evan Morgan," typescript photocopy, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2011)
    - Kempner, Mary Jean: "Notes from Baffin Island," printed version, Harper's Magazine, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 2012)
    - Kempner, Mary Jean, Invitation to Portugal, review of, [Dallas?] Morning News, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 2013)
    - Kirkup, James, "Evening Rain: Correy Street, York," holograph poem, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2014)
    - Mambrino, Jean, three prose poems, typescript and typescript carbon, 1946-50, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2015)
      See also: Series I, Correspondence, Box 14, Folder 775
    - Morgan, Evan (Viscount Tredegar), poems, manuscript, typescript, and typescript carbon, 1926-33 (Box 44, Folder 2016)
      "Hymn to Christ the King"
      "Think not the nights grown long"
      "Paris, a song"
      "Had I forgotten You"
      "The Poet--a riddle"
      "Broken Echo"
    - Pollard, F. E., "The Word They Never Said Aloud," story, typescript, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2017)
    - Singer, Burns
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 23, Folder 1112
    - Squire, John Collings, Sir, "Introduction" [to the works of Jane Austen], holograph manuscript, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2018)
    - Stern, James
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 23, Folder 1154
    - Stevenson, Quentin
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 23, Folder 1158
    - Stevenson, Robert Louis, "Songs of a Child," typescript mimeograph, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2019)
      [To be sung to music by
      Geertruida Vogel?]
    - Talese, Gay, "Author's Note" on his The Kingdom and the Power, typescript photocopy, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 2020)
    - Thomas, Dylan
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 24, Folder 1190
    - Todd, Olivier, "New Realism," script for BBC broadcast, typescript, 1958 May 13 (Box 44, Folder 2021)
    - Weintraub, Stanley, "Bernard Shaw's Other Saint Joan," reprint, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 2022)
    - "R.J.H.[O.?]," "Some Leprechauns, Ireland, and Other Things," typescript carbon, corrected (Box 44, Folder 2023)
    - Unidentified authors: poems and prose fragments, manuscript and typescript, 1927-59, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2024)
      Includes essay printed in
      Oxford magazine The Isis with letters to the editor
      by APJ in response; also
      includes photocopy of an
      unattributed poem, printed in
      a book, signed on the original
      "Tennessee [Williams]--with
      apologies"
- Photographs, [ca.1860]-1995; Series III; 0.83; (2 boxes)
  Series III, Photographs, is
  organized into four subseries:
  Alan Pryce-Jones; Friends and
  Family; Unidentified People
  and Places. The arrangement of
  each is noted under the subseries
  heading when appropriate
  - ALAN PRYCE-JONES
    - Photograph album, 1908-[ca.1925]
      Childhood portraits, with
      Henry Morris Pryce-Jones,
      Vere Dawnay Pryce-Jones, and
      Adrian Pryce-Jones
    - Loose photograph from album, [ca. 1910] (Box 45, Folder 2025)
    - Childhood photographs, [ca. 1909-20] (Box 45, Folder 2026)
      With Henry Morris Pryce-Jones,
      Vere Dawnay Pryce-Jones,
      and Adrian Pryce-Jones
      See also: Series II, Writings, Diaries, "Fishers Sate," 1920, Box 47, folder 2083
    - Studio portraits, [ca. 1927-32] (Box 45, Folder 2027)
    - Studio portraits, 1932-61, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 2028)
      One by Horst, several by
      Lotte Meitner-Graf, and others
    - APJ on pilgrimage to Lourdes, 1957 Sep 27, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 2029)
    - Passport photographs, [ca. 1960-80] (Box 45, Folder 2030)
    - Snapshots, [ca. 1960]-93 (Box 45, Folder 2031)
    - Portraits taken by Bob Thayer, Providence Journal-Bulletin, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 2032)
    - APJ with unidentified people, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 2033)
      See also: Series I, Correspondence, Derek Hill, Box 12, folder 585
      See also: Series I, Correspondence, Malcolm Bullock, Box 6, folder 210
  - FRIENDS AND FAMILY
    - Barker, Ray, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 2034)
      Printed reproduction
    - Bernstein, Leonard, and family
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Bernstein, Box 2, Folder 99
    - Buccleuch, Mary, Duchess of, 1962-78, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 2035)
      With APJ, Roy Harrod, Billa
      Harrod, Osbert Lancaster,
      Randolph Churchill, David and
      Oliver Gilmour, and others
      unidentified
      See also: Series I, Correspondence, Buccleuch, Box 3-6, folders 171-207
    - Clark, Kenneth, [1978?] (Box 45, Folder 2036)
      With APJ, Viscount
      and Viscountess Gage
    - Connolly, Cyril and Jean, 1933 [Aug 25] (Box 45, Folder 2037)
      Photos from a party given by
      the Connollys at Bazehill
      House, Rottingdean, with APJ,
      [Joan Eyres-Monsell?], Brian
      Howard, Eddie Gathorne-Hardy,
      Peter Quennell, others (possibly
      Piers Synott, John Strachey,
      Mrs. Peter Quennell, Tom
      Bakewell, Nigel Richards,
      Enid Bagnold), and two lemurs
    - Dawnay, Lewis Payan, 1910
      See: Series IV, Family History, Lewis Dawnay, Box 64, Folder 2399
    - Eccles, Mary Hyde, and Lila Hotz Luce Tyng, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 2038)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, Jr., and Mary Lee Fairbanks
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Fairbanks, Box 9, Folder 404
    - Gilmour, Ian and Caroline (Box 45, Folder 2039)
      With APJ, David and/or Oliver
      Gilmour, and unidentified man,
      at Boughton House
      See also: Series I, Correspondence, Gilmour, Caroline, Box 10, folder 467
    - Gorman, Douglas and David, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 2040)
    - Grey, William, and Mrs. William Grey, [ca. 1860] (Box 45, Folder 2041)
      One-half of a stereo view; also
      identified as "Drawing room,
      Elghammar;" includes two men
      and one woman
    - Harris, Cara (work of)
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Michael Parkin, Box 16, folder 909
    - Harrod, Billa, and APJ (Box 45, Folder 2042)
    - Hudson, Larry, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 2043)
      With APJ
    - Kempner, Mary Jean, [1968], n.d. (Box 45, Folder 2044)
      One studio portrait of her
      one with APJ
    - Kostial, Amelie, 1956 Oct 20 (Box 45, Folder 2045)
    - Mambrino, Jean
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Mambrino, Box 14, Folder 775
    - Margaret, Princess, Countess of Snowdon, and APJ, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 2046)
    - Maugham, W. Somerset, and APJ, an interview, [1955] (Box 45, Folder 2047)
    - Maugham, W. Somerset (group of photos labeled "Renishaw, Mauresque, 1933") (Box 45, Folder 2048)
      W. S. Maugham and others
      unidentified; APJ on the
      beach; also one photo
      possibly taken at Renishaw
      Hall, and one in Germany or
      Austria
    - Mitford, Unity, and Diana Mosley, in front of Nazi troops and flags, [1930s] (Box 45, Folder 2049)
    - Morgan, Evan (Viscount Tredegar), 1927 (Box 45, Folder 2050)
      See also: "Corsica 1932," Box 46, folder 2061
    - Pryce-Jones, Adam, [ca. 1975] (Box 45, Folder 2051)
    - Pryce-Jones, Candida, and Owen Mostyn-Owen, [1989 Jul 15] (Box 45, Folder 2052)
    - Pryce-Jones, David, [ca.1943]-60 (Box 45, Folder 2053)
      Photograph dated 1960
      includes Clarissa Caccia
      See also: Series I, Correspondence, letter from Thérèse Pryce-Jones to "Nana," Box 27, folder 1425
    - Pryce-Jones, Henry Morris, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 2054)
    - Pryce-Jones, Henry Morris and Vere, gravestone of (Box 46, Folder 2055)
    - Pryce-Jones, Jessica, [ca. 1963-80] (Box 46, Folder 2056)
    - Pryce-Jones, Thérèse Fould-Springer, [ca. 1925]-50 (Box 46, Folder 2057)
      One studio portrait, and snapshots
      with APJ, Liliane de Rothschild,
      Max Fould-Springer, Hélène Propper
      de Callejon, and others; also
      one drawing and one photograph
      of a drawing, both portraits
      in profile, 1933-34
    - Rothschild, Cecile de, 1983-95, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2058)
      With APJ and Henry J. Heinz
    - Rothschild, Elie and Liliane de, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 2059)
      Photograph by Karl Lagerfeld
    - "Treason's Bargain," cast photograph, n.d.
      Copy of 1937 photo, includes
      John Betjeman, Cecil Beaton,
      Lord Berners, [Freddie Chiltern?],
      Adrian Daintry, Lord Donegall,
      Simon Harcourt-Smith, Zita James,
      Osbert Lancaster, Fluff Willes,
      and Vere [?]
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Michael Parkin, Box 16, Folder 909
    - Postcards, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2060)
      Contains portraits of Prince
      Baltazar Carlos of Spain,
      Albert Camus, and Alfred
      Thayer Mahan
  - UNIDENTIFIED PEOPLE
    - "Corsica 1932" (Box 46, Folder 2061)
      Unidentified people, landscapes,
      and towns; three of the photos
      are possibly not Corsica, one
      of these includes [Evan Morgan?]
    - [Wedding?] at Christ Church, [1920s] (Box 46, Folder 2062)
    - Victorian couple, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2063)
    - Woman and three men, with dog (Box 46, Folder 2064)
    - People, general, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2065)
      See also: Southeast Asia and Villa S. Martino folders below, Box 46, folder 2078, Box 46, folder 2073
  - PLACES
    - Britain
      - Boughton House, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2066)
      - Fishers Sate
        See: Series II, Diaries, Box 47, Folder 2083
      - Hatch Manor, Tisbury
        See: Series I, James Stern, Box 23, Folder 1154
      - [Howick or Beningbrough?], photographs of a painting, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2067)
      - Rochecotte
        See: Series II, Diaries, Box 47, Folder 2089
      - Syon House (postcards), n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2068)
      - [Windsor Castle?] (Box 46, Folder 2069)
    - Europe
      - Montreuil-sur-mer, 1 Parvis Saint-Fermin, Pas-de-Calais, France (postcard), n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2070)
      - Royaumont, Par Asnières-sur-Oise, France (postcards), n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2071)
      - Springer family house in Meidling, Austria (postcards), n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2072)
      - Villa S. Martino, Florence, Italy, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2073)
        Group includes three photos
        of unidentified women on
        boat, New York
    - United States
      - 46 John Street, Newport, Rhode Island (Box 46, Folder 2074)
      - "Price House," by Bruce Goff, plan and two interior views, Oklahoma (Box 46, Folder 2075)
    - Other
      - South America, general views, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2076)
      - Brasilia, Brazil (postcards), n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2077)
      - Southeast Asia, [ca. 1960s] (Box 46, Folder 2078)
        With unidentified people
      - Travel photos, unidentified place, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2079)
      - Unidentified houses, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2080)
      - Various places (postcards), n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2081)
- Personal Papers, 1857-2000; Series IV; 7.5; (18 boxes)
  Series IV, Personal Papers,
  is organized into six subseries:
  Diaries; Financial Papers
  Official Documents and Related
  Material; Professional (Non-
  Literary) Work; Other Papers
  and Family Papers. The arrangement
  of each is noted under the subseries
  heading or other subheading where
  appropriate.
  - DIARIES
    - Journal Diaries
      - Diary: 1918, holograph (Box 47, Folder 2082)
      - "Golden Memories: Fishers Sate," May to June 1920, holograph (Box 47, Folder 2083)
        Contains photographs of APJ,
        and their dog
      - Diaries: 1920, 1921, holograph, 1920-21 (Box 47, Folder 2084)
      - "Golden Memories III: Long Parish," August 1922, holograph (Box 47, Folder 2085)
      - Diaries: 1922, 1923, holograph, 1922-23 (Box 47, Folder 2086)
      - Diaries: 1924, 1925, holograph, 1924-25 (Box 47, Folder 2087)
      - Diary: Trip to Bruges, January 6-10, holograph, [1926] Jan (Box 47, Folder 2088)
      - Diaries: 1926 (2), holograph (Box 47, Folder 2089)
        Diary for September to December
        contains photograph of Rochecotte
        and photograph of unidentified
        house
      - Diary: October 1927 to February 1933, holograph, 1927-33 (Box 48, Folder 2090)
      - Diary: January to June, holograph, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 2091)
      - Diary: December 1930 to October 1931, holograph, 1930-31 (Box 48, Folder 2092)
      - "Andean Diary," typescript, corrected, of portions of 1930-31 diary (Box 48, Folder 2093)
      - Diary: October 1931 to August 1932, holograph, 1931-32 (Box 48, Folder 2094)
      - Diary: August 1932 to September 1934, holograph, 1932-34 (Box 48, Folder 2095)
      - Diary: January 1935 to November 1937, holograph, 1935-37 (Box 49, Folder 2096)
      - Diary: February 1938 to March 1958, holograph, 1938-58 (Box 49, Folder 2097)
      - Diary: October [1939]; March to December 1940; May [1941]; February to May 1977, holograph, 19[39-41], 1977 (Box 49, Folder 2098)
      - Diary: September 1941 to March 1943, holograph, 1941-43 (Box 49, Folder 2099)
      - Diary: 11-21 August 1948, holograph (Box 49, Folder 2100)
      - Diary: March to April 1956, holograph (Box 49, Folder 2101)
      - Diary: August 1955 to May 1960, typescript, 1955-60 (Box 50, Folder 2102-2103)
      - Diary: February to December 1962, typescript (Box 50, Folder 2104-2106)
      - Diary: January to December 1963, typescript (Box 50, Folder 2107-2108)
      - Diary: January to December 1964, typescript (Box 50, Folder 2109-2110)
      - Diary: January to December 1965, typescript (Box 50, Folder 2111-2112)
      - Diary: January to December 1966, typescript (Box 50, Folder 2113-2114)
      - Diary: January to December 1967, typescript (Box 50, Folder 2115-2116)
      - Diary: January to December 1968, typescript photocopy and typescript (Box 51, Folder 2117-2118)
      - Diary: January to December 1969, typescript (Box 51, Folder 2119-2120)
        Page 35 missing when received
        memorial essay about Ivy
        Compton-Burnett follows
        December 31 entry
      - Diary: January to December 1970, typescript (Box 51, Folder 2121)
        Page 20 missing when received
      - Diary: January to December 1971, typescrpt (Box 51, Folder 2122-2123)
      - Diary: January to December 1972, typescript (Box 51, Folder 2124)
      - Diary: January to December 1973, typescript (Box 51, Folder 2125-2126)
      - Diary: January to December 1974, typescript (Box 51, Folder 2127)
      - Diary: January to December 1975, typescript (Box 51, Folder 2128-2129)
      - Diary: January to December 1976, typescript (Box 51, Folder 2130-2131)
      - Diary: January to December 1977, typescript (Box 51, Folder 2132-2133)
        See also: Diary, [1939-41] Box 49, Folder 2098 for February to May 1977
      - Diary: January to December 1978, typescript (Box 51, Folder 2134-2135)
      - Diary: January to December 1979, typescript (Box 51, Folder 2136-2137)
      - Diary: January to December 1980, typesript (Box 52, Folder 2138-2139)
      - Diary: January to December 1981, typescript (Box 52, Folder 2140-2141)
      - Diary/notebook, holograph, 1981, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 2142)
      - Diary: January to December 1982, typescript (Box 52, Folder 2143-2144)
      - Diary: January to December 1983, typescript (Box 52, Folder 2145-2146)
      - Diary: January to December 1984, typescript (Box 52, Folder 2147-2148)
      - Diary: January to December 1985, typescript (Box 52, Folder 2149-2150)
      - Diary: January to December 1986, typescript (Box 52, Folder 2151-2152)
      - Diary: January to December 1987, typescript (Box 52, Folder 2153-2154)
      - Diary: January to December 1988, typescript (Box 52, Folder 2155-2156)
      - Diary: January to October 1989, typescript (Box 52, Folder 2157)
      - Diary: "Anecdotage," holograph, 1992 Feb 2 (Box 53, Folder 2158)
      - Diary: [Russia?], holograph, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 2159)
    - Engagement Calendars
      - Eton assignment notebooks, 1920-24, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 2160-2162)
        Accompanied by English Literature
        Prize questions
      - Pocket calendars for 1922, 1925, and 1926, 1922-26 (Box 53, Folder 2163)
      - Pocket calendars for 1930, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 2164)
      - Pocket calendar for 1935 (Box 53, Folder 2165)
      - Pocket calendars for 1936 [2] (Box 53, Folder 2166)
      - Pocket calendars for 1937 [3] (Box 53, Folder 2167)
      - Pocket calendars for 1938 [3] (Box 53, Folder 2168)
        One of the three belonged
        to Thérèse Pryce-Jones
      - Pocket calendars for 1939, 1940, 1939-40 (Box 54, Folder 2169)
      - Pocket calendars for 1941 [3] (Box 54, Folder 2170)
      - Pocket calendar for 1942 (Box 54, Folder 2171)
      - "Year by Year" calendar, 1943-47 (Box 54, Folder 2172)
      - Pocket calendars for 1944, 1945, 1946, 1945-46 (Box 54, Folder 2173)
      - Pocket calendars for 1947, 1948, 1947-48 (Box 54, Folder 2174)
      - "Year by Year" calendar, 1948-55 (Box 54, Folder 2175)
      - Pocket and desk calendar for 1949 [2] (Box 54, Folder 2176)
      - Pocket calendars for 1950, 1951, 1950-51 (Box 54, Folder 2177)
      - Pocket calendars for 1952 [2] (Box 55, Folder 2178)
      - Pocket calendars for 1953, 1954, 1953-54 (Box 55, Folder 2179)
      - Pocket calendars for 1955, 1956, 1956-56 (Box 55, Folder 2180)
      - Pocket calendars for 1957 [2] (Box 55, Folder 2181)
      - Pocket calendars for 1958, 1959, 1958-59 (Box 55, Folder 2182)
      - Pocket calendars for 1960 [2], 1961, 1960-61 (Box 55, Folder 2183)
      - Pocket and desk calendars for 1962 [2] (Box 55, Folder 2184)
      - Pocket calendars for 1963, 1964, 1963-64 (Box 55, Folder 2185)
      - Pocket calendars for 1965, 1966, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 2186)
      - Pocket calendars for 1967, 1968, 1969, 1967-69 (Box 55, Folder 2187)
      - Pocket calendars for 1970 [2] (Box 55, Folder 2188)
      - Pocket calendars for 1971, 1972, 1971-72 (Box 55, Folder 2189)
      - Pocket calendars for 1973, 1974, 1973-74 (Box 56, Folder 2190)
      - Pocket calendars for 1975, 1976 [2], 1975-76 (Box 56, Folder 2191)
      - Pocket calendars for 1977, 1978, 1977-78 (Box 56, Folder 2192)
      - Pocket calendars for 1979, 1980, 1979-80 (Box 56, Folder 2193)
      - Pocket calendars for 1981, 1982, 1981-82 (Box 56, Folder 2194)
      - Pocket calendars for 1983 [2] (Box 56, Folder 2195)
      - Pocket calendars for 1984 [2] (Box 56, Folder 2196)
      - Pocket calendars for 1985, 1986, 1985-86 (Box 56, Folder 2197)
      - Pocket calendars for 1987, 1989, 1987-89 (Box 56, Folder 2198)
      - Pocket calendars for 1990, 1991, 1990-91 (Box 56, Folder 2199)
      - Pocket calendars for 1992 [2] (Box 56, Folder 2200)
      - Pocket calendars for 1993, 1994, 1993-94 (Box 57, Folder 2201)
      - Pocket calendar for 1995 (Box 57, Folder 2202)
  - FINANCIAL PAPERS
    - Correspondence and Statements
      - Amsterdam Overseas Corporation, 1964-65 (Box 57, Folder 2203)
      - A. P. Watt Ltd., 1968-87 (Box 57, Folder 2204)
      - Bankers Trust Company, 1970-96 (Box 57, Folder 2205-2207)
      - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1961-94 (Box 57, Folder 2208)
      - Coudert Brothers/Civil Court of the City of New York, 1961-67 (Box 57, Folder 2209)
      - Credit Card Service Bureau, 1978-88 (Box 57, Folder 2210)
      - Dawnay, Day & Co., Ltd., 1946-58 (Box 57, Folder 2211)
      - Dixon Wilson & Co., Chartered Accountants, 1973-91 (Box 57, Folder 2212)
      - E. F. Turner & Sons, 1972 May 8 (Box 57, Folder 2213)
      - Eland Hore Pattersons, Solicitors, 1960-69 (Box 57, Folder 2214)
      - Great Britain. Board of Inland Revenue, 1967 Oct 25 (Box 57, Folder 2215)
      - Great Britain. Foreign Office, 1941-55 (Box 57, Folder 2216)
      - Great Britain. Trading with the Enemy Department, 1946 (Box 57, Folder 2217)
      - The Halcyon Foundation, 1965-89 (Box 57, Folder 2218)
      - Herbert Oppenheimer, Nathan & Vandyk, 1946-47 (Box 57, Folder 2219)
      - Hickman, J. M. J., 1940-65, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 2220)
      - Kidd Rapinet, Solicitors, 1993-95 (Box 57, Folder 2221)
      - John Dubé, Q. C., 1961-67 (Box 57, Folder 2222)
      - Lloyd's Bank Limited, 1945-94 (Box 57, Folder 2223-2224)
      - Newport, City of, 1978-92 (Box 57, Folder 2225)
      - Norton, Rose, Botterell & Roche, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 2226)
      - Percy A. Popkin & Co., Accountants & Auditors/H. E. Madams, A.F.A., 1953-65 (Box 58, Folder 2227)
      - Redwood Library and Athenaeum, 1964-73 (Box 58, Folder 2228)
      - Rhode Island Hospital Trust National Bank, 1972-91 (Box 58, Folder 2229)
      - Richards, Layton & Finger, 1976-80 (Box 58, Folder 2230)
      - Rothschild Asset Management Inc./ New Court Securities, 1969-93 (Box 58, Folder 2231)
      - Royal Literary Fund, Balance Sheets, 1958 Dec 31 (Box 58, Folder 2232)
      - Singer & Friedlander, Ltd., 1942-61 (Box 58, Folder 2233)
      - Stern & Reubens, 1964-65 (Box 58, Folder 2234)
      - State of New York. Department of Motor Vehicles, 1962-79 (Box 58, Folder 2235)
      - State of Rhode Island. Department of Employment Security, 1985-86 (Box 58, Folder 2236)
      - Stroock & Stroock & Lavan, 1992-93 (Box 58, Folder 2237)
      - Sugarland Industries, 1975-76 (Box 58, Folder 2238)
      - TIAA CREF, 1965-92 (Box 58, Folder 2239)
      - The Times (London), 1947-92 (Box 58, Folder 2240)
      - U. S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare. Social Security Administration, [1960]-92 (Box 58, Folder 2241)
      - Webster Sheffield Fleischmann Hitchcock & Brookfield, 1969-73 (Box 58, Folder 2242)
      - Weissberger & Frosch, Counselors at Law/Howard O. LeShaw, 1961-74 (Box 58, Folder 2243)
      - Westminster Bank Limited, 1947-63 (Box 58, Folder 2244)
      - Wooster, Mary, power of attorney and copy of letter to Hambros Bank, 1938-46 (Box 58, Folder 2245)
      - 1988 tax information (Box 58, Folder 2246)
      - Miscellaneous bank receipts and statements, 1948-89 (Box 58, Folder 2247)
      - Miscellaneous paystubs, 1958-62 (Box 58, Folder 2248)
      - Lists of expenses, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 2249)
    - Insurance
      - AARP/Prudential, 1979-93 (Box 58, Folder 2250)
      - Blue Cross Blue Shield/Medicare, 1969-95 (Box 58, Folder 2251-2252)
      - Ford Foundation Group Insurance Protection Plans, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 2253)
      - Henry Head & Co. Ltd., 1960-61 (Box 58, Folder 2254)
      - Kirby, Inc., general correspondence, 1962-89 (Box 58, Folder 2255)
      - Kirby, Inc./Fireman's Fund Insurance, 1983-94 (Box 59, Folder 2256-2257)
      - Kirby, Inc./Reliance Insurance Company, 1964-88 (Box 59, Folder 2258)
      - London Life Association Limited, 1936-61 (Box 59, Folder 2259)
        See also: Oversize, Box 65, Folder 2435
      - Legal & General Assurance Society Limited, 1992-93 (Box 59, Folder 2260)
      - Scottish Widows' Fund & Life Assurance Society, 1948-80 (Box 59, Folder 2261)